Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[Echoes of the Self]
[أصداء الذات]
Brother.
أخ.
I've ordered people
لقد أمرت الناس
to close the Military Supply Route.
لإغلاق طريق الإمدادات العسكرية.
Zhou Kui can't transport his arms and ordnance in.
لا يستطيع تشو كوي نقل أسلحته وذخائره.
I'm afraid Zhou Kui
أنا خائف من تشو كوي
still has a backup plan.
لا يزال لديه خطة احتياطية.
How did I not notice
كيف لم ألاحظ
Zhou Kui's treacherous ambitions before?
طموحات تشو كوي الغادرة من قبل؟
Brother,
أخ،
you used to
كنت تستخدم
see him only as your father-in-law.
لا تنظر إليه إلا كحموك.
You were too busy trying to please him.
لقد كنت مشغولاً جدًا بمحاولة إرضائه.
So how could you
فكيف يمكنك ذلك؟
be suspicious of him?
هل تشك فيه؟
Why have you been with the Princess
لماذا كنت مع الأميرة؟
for so long that
لفترة طويلة لدرجة أن
your tongue has become so sharp?
لقد أصبح لسانك حادًا جدًا؟
I think it's better this way.
أعتقد أن الأمر أفضل بهذه الطريقة.
Always holding back and pleasing others
دائما ما يتراجع ويسعى لإرضاء الآخرين
is exhausting.
مرهق.
Yan,
نعم،
you seem to know her well.
يبدو أنك تعرفها جيدًا.
I've known her for two lifetimes.
لقد عرفتها منذ عمرين.
How could I not know her well?
كيف لا أعرفها جيدا؟
Brother,
أخ،
don't blame her.
لا تلومها.
She's just been through too much
لقد مرت بالكثير
and harbors hatred toward you.
ويحمل الكراهية نحوك.
Hatred?
كراهية؟
I just can't understand
انا لا استطيع الفهم
where this hatred
أين هذه الكراهية
comes from.
يأتي من.
Is it merely because
هل هو فقط لأنه
I previously suspected her
لقد كنت أشك بها من قبل
of orchestrating the assassination?
من هو المسؤول عن تدبير عملية الاغتيال؟
Brother,
أخ،
right now
الآن
we're facing a great enemy.
نحن نواجه عدوًا عظيمًا.
The most important thing is
الشيء الأكثر أهمية هو
whether you and Fu Wei can resolve your differences
هل يمكنك أنت وفو وي حل خلافاتكما؟
and work together.
والعمل معا.
Hmm.
همم.
Also,
أيضًا،
Brother,
أخ،
there are things
هناك أشياء
you need to tell her yourself.
يجب عليك أن تخبرها بنفسك.
We are both princes of Yunrui,
نحن الاثنان أمراء يونروي،
yet now we're worrying ourselves sick over the women we love.
ولكننا الآن نقلق بشدة بشأن النساء اللواتي نحبهن.
If Father found out,
إذا اكتشف الأب،
he would surely scold us
إنه بالتأكيد سوف يوبخنا
for being pathetic.
لكونه مثير للشفقة.
I'm thinking,
انا أفكر
after everything settles down,
بعد أن يستقر كل شيء،
we'll go find Ruoyao
سنذهب للبحث عن روياو
and travel the world together,
ونسافر حول العالم معًا،
living carefree lives.
عيش حياة خالية من الهموم.
I hope that day
أتمنى ذلك اليوم
comes soon.
يأتي قريبا.
Crown Prince Shu,
ولي العهد شو،
you wanted to see me?
هل تريد رؤيتي؟
Did you call me here to listen to the rain?
هل اتصلت بي هنا للاستماع إلى المطر؟
I
أنا
asked you to come here today
طلبت منك أن تأتي إلى هنا اليوم
to apologize for everything
للاعتذار عن كل شيء
that happened before
الذي حدث من قبل
and ask for your forgiveness.
وأطلب مغفرتك.
What you should apologize for
ما الذي يجب عليك الاعتذار عنه
is more than just this.
هو أكثر من هذا فقط.
I still don't understand
انا لا افهم بعد
where all your hatred toward me
حيث كل كراهيتك لي
comes from.
يأتي من.
Do you really want to know?
هل تريد حقا أن تعرف؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Now
الآن
we're even.
نحن متعادلون.
Li Shu,
لي شو,
there will be no more hatred
لن يكون هناك المزيد من الكراهية
between us
بيننا
from now on.
من الآن فصاعدا.
Yan is right.
يان على حق.
Since I've been given a second life,
منذ أن حصلت على حياة ثانية،
I shouldn't be burdened by the shackles of the past.
لا ينبغي لي أن أثقل كاهلي بقيود الماضي.
Crown Prince Shu,
ولي العهد شو،
you should return to your residence soon.
ينبغي عليك العودة إلى مقر إقامتك قريبا.
There's still a play
لا يزال هناك مسرحية
that you need to perform.
التي تحتاج إلى القيام بها.
Also,
أيضًا،
I would trouble you
سأزعجك
to deliver a message for me.
لتوصيل رسالة لي.
It's been several days,
لقد مرت عدة أيام،
and there's still no sign of His Highness.
ولا يزال لا يوجد أي أثر لسموه.
It seems I can't hide it anymore.
يبدو أنني لم أعد أستطيع إخفاء الأمر بعد الآن.
Xi.
شي.
Father.
أب.
It's so late.
لقد فات الأوان.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
I've come to see His Highness
لقد جئت لرؤية سموه
to report some matters.
للإبلاغ عن بعض الأمور.
Where is His Highness?
أين سموه؟
Are you hiding something
هل تخفي شيئا؟
from me?
مني؟
Has the Crown Prince gone missing?
هل اختفى ولي العهد؟
No.
لا.
His Highness is here in the mansion.
صاحب السمو موجود هنا في القصر.
He...
هو...
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك،
we're in the same boat now.
نحن في نفس القارب الآن.
Don't you dare try
لا تجرؤ على المحاولة
any tricks with me!
أي حيل معي!
I wouldn't dare.
لا أجرؤ على ذلك.
Then where is he?
ثم أين هو؟
Keep drinking!
استمر بالشرب!
Lord Zhou!
اللورد تشو!
Let's continue!
دعونا نستمر!
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Don't leave.
لا تغادر.
Keep drinking.
استمر بالشرب.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
let me attend to you.
دعني أهتم بك.
Don't you touch me!
لا تلمسني!
Who are you really?
من أنت حقا؟
What's wrong, Your Highness?
ما الأمر يا صاحب السمو؟
I'm Fu Wei, your Crown Princess.
أنا فو وي، ولي عهدك.
I know you're not her.
أعرف أنك لست هي.
My Crown Princess...
أميرتي التاج...
My Crown Princess isn't that ugly!
أميرتي التاج ليست قبيحة إلى هذه الدرجة!
Lord Zhou!
اللورد تشو!
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
Keep...
يحفظ...
Keep drinking.
استمر بالشرب.
Drunk like this,
سكران مثل هذا،
he hardly looks like an heir to the throne.
إنه لا يبدو وكأنه وريث العرش.
Father,
أب،
His Highness
صاحب السمو
has been drinking every day
لقد كان يشرب كل يوم
because of what happened to Ruoyao.
بسبب ما حدث لروياو.
He hasn't attended to state affairs for days.
لم يحضر شؤون الدولة منذ أيام.
That's fine.
هذا جيّد.
If he's so lovesick,
إذا كان مريضًا بالحب إلى هذا الحد،
then let's make him never wake up.
إذن فلنجعله لا يستيقظ أبدًا.
Come.
يأتي.
This is Xiaoyao Powder.
هذا هو مسحوق شياوياو.
Mix it into
اخلطه في
his meals every day.
وجباته اليومية.
Soon,
قريباً،
the state of Yunrui
ولاية يونروي
will be in our hands.
سيكون في أيدينا.
His Majesty is still in power.
جلالته لا يزال في السلطة.
His Highness
صاحب السمو
hasn't inherited the throne yet.
لم يرث العرش بعد
How can we seize power?
كيف نستطيع الإستيلاء على السلطة؟
Don't worry about that.
لا تقلق بشأن ذلك.
Just do as I say.
فقط افعل كما أقول .
Just remember this.
فقط تذكر هذا .
I can raise you above thousands,
أستطيع أن أرفعك فوق الآلاف،
but I can also make you
ولكن يمكنني أن أجعلك أيضا
fall into eternal damnation.
الوقوع في الهلاك الأبدي.
Take it.
خذها.
Take it!
خذها!
Don't you touch me!
لا تلمسني!
You're here.
أنت هنا.
Why did you ask me to come here?
لماذا طلبت مني المجيء إلى هنا؟
Today's Mother's birthday.
اليوم عيد ميلاد أمي.
I was afraid you'd forget.
كنت خائفة من أن تنسى.
My mother's affairs
شؤون والدتي
are none of your business.
لا شأن لك.
Xi,
شي،
even now, don't you understand
حتى الآن، ألا تفهم؟
why Mother died
لماذا ماتت أمي
and who killed her?
ومن قتلها؟
She discovered Zhou Kui was from the Daqing royal family,
اكتشفت أن تشو كوي كان من العائلة المالكة داتشينغ،
so Zhou Kui got rid of her through Madam Cui's hands.
لذلك تخلص تشو كوي منها على يد السيدة كوي.
Mother was killed by Father?
هل قتلت الأم على يد الأب؟
Why would he do that?
لماذا يفعل ذلك؟
Zhou Kui has been plotting for years,
لقد كان تشو كوي يخطط لسنوات،
all for that one day
كل ذلك من أجل ذلك اليوم الواحد
he could seize power.
كان بإمكانه الاستيلاء على السلطة.
He won't let anyone who knows his secret live.
لن يسمح لأحد يعرف سره بالعيش.
He's hiding your identity now
إنه يخفي هويتك الآن
just to make you a pawn in his game,
فقط لجعلك بيدقًا في لعبته،
a stepping stone.
حجر الأساس.
Even if what you say is true,
حتى لو كان ما تقوله صحيحا،
what difference does it make?
ما الفرق الذي يحدثه ذلك؟
Mother is already dead.
الأم ماتت بالفعل.
In this world,
في هذا العالم،
Father is my only support.
أبي هو دعمي الوحيد.
Since he's willing
لأنه راغب
to raise me above all others,
لرفعني فوق كل الآخرين،
then I'm willing
ثم أنا على استعداد
to be his pawn
أن تكون بيدقه
and stepping stone.
وحجر الدوس.
Xi,
شي،
why won't you turn back even now?
لماذا لا تعود حتى الآن؟
One turns back when there's a way out.
الإنسان يعود عندما يكون هناك مخرج.
But now,
ولكن الآن،
beneath my feet are mountains of blades and seas of fire,
تحت قدمي جبال من النصال وبحار من النار،
and behind me is a bottomless abyss.
وخلف ظهري هاوية لا نهاية لها.
What way out do I have?
ما هو المخرج الذي أملكه؟
How can I turn back?
كيف يمكنني الرجوع؟
Everywhere in this world
في كل مكان في هذا العالم
is like a prison.
هو مثل السجن.
Now that you have a second life,
الآن وقد أصبحت لديك حياة ثانية،
you shouldn't be trapped here.
لا ينبغي أن تبقى محاصرا هنا.
Mother's affairs,
شؤون الأم،
the Zhou family's business,
أعمال عائلة تشو،
even the politics of Yunrui court—
حتى سياسة محكمة يونروي؟؟؟
none of them concerns you.
لا شيء منهم يهمك.
You should leave this place
يجب عليك مغادرة هذا المكان
and find somewhere you can be free.
وإيجاد مكان يمكنك أن تكون فيه حرا.
Xi.
شي.
Xi!
شي!
[Happiness]
[سعادة]
Yan,
نعم،
in this second life,
في هذه الحياة الثانية،
your determination
تصميمك
has spared me from regret.
لقد أنقذني من الندم.
However,
لكن،
the rest of our days will be difficult.
وسوف تكون بقية أيامنا صعبة.
We don't know how many days we have left.
نحن لا نعلم كم يوما بقي لنا.
No matter how many days remain,
مهما تبقى من أيام،
as long as I'm with you,
طالما أنا معك
this life
هذه الحياة
[Happiness]
[سعادة]
will be complete.
سوف تكون كاملة.
This young lady
هذه الشابة
is already at the end of her life.
هي بالفعل في نهاية حياتها.
Your Highness, once your fate is linked with hers,
صاحب السمو، بمجرد أن يرتبط مصيرك بمصيرها،
sharing your lifespan with her,
مشاركة حياتك معها،
your physical deterioration will increase daily,
سوف يزداد تدهورك الجسدي يوميا،
and there's no way to reverse it.
وليس هناك طريقة لعكس ذلك.
Can you
هل تستطيع
handle that?
التعامل مع ذلك؟
I
أنا
would never regret it.
لن أندم على ذلك أبدًا.
[Prince Yan's Mansion]
[قصر الأمير يان]
Congratulations!
مبروك!
[Virtuous Virtue]
[الفضيلة الفاضلة]
First bow to heaven and earth!
أول إنحناء للسماء والأرض!
Bow.
قَوس.
Second bow to the parents!
التحية الثانية للوالدين!
Today,
اليوم،
I am greatly comforted
أنا مرتاح للغاية
that all my sons have established families,
أن جميع أبنائي لديهم عائلات مستقرة،
and the state affairs
وشؤون الدولة
can be entrusted to you.
يمكن أن يعهد إليك.
Husband and wife bow to each other!
الزوج والزوجة ينحنيان لبعضهما البعض!
Bow.
قَوس.
Wait!
انتظر!